const htmlQuestions = [
    {
        question: "1: What does HTML stand for?",
        choices: [
            "Hypertext Markup Language",
            "Hyperlink and Text Markup Language",
            "Home Tool Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinking Text Marking Language"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2: Who is making the Web standards?",
        choices: [
            "Mozilla",
            "Google",
            "The World Wide Web Consortium",
            "Microsoft"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "3: Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:",
        choices: [
            "&lt;heading&gt;",
            "&lt;h6&gt;",
            "&lt;head&gt;",
            "&lt;h1&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "4: What is the correct HTML element for inserting a line break?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;br&gt;",
            "&lt;break&gt;",
            "&lt;lb&gt;",
            "&lt;line&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "5: What is the correct HTML for adding a background color?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;body style='background-color:yellow;'&gt;",
            "&lt;body bg='yellow'&gt;",
            "&lt;background&gt;yellow&lt;/background&gt;",
            "&lt;body background='yellow'&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "6: Choose the correct HTML element to define important text",
        choices: [
            "&lt;important&gt;",
            "&lt;strong&gt;",
            "&lt;b&gt;",
            "&lt;i&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "7: How can you make a numbered list?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;ol&gt;",
            "&lt;list&gt;",
            "&lt;ul&gt;",
            "&lt;dl&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "8: How can you make a bulleted list?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;ol&gt;",
            "&lt;ul&gt;",
            "&lt;list&gt;",
            "&lt;dl&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "9: What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;a&gt;http://www.example.com&lt;/a&gt;",
            "&lt;a href='http://www.example.com'&gt;Example&lt;/a&gt;",
            "&lt;link href='http://www.example.com'&gt;",
            "&lt;a url='http://www.example.com'&gt;Example&lt;/a&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "10: Which character is used to indicate an end tag?",
        choices: [
            "*",
            "/",
            "&lt;",
            "^"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "11: How can you open a link in a new tab/browser window?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;a href='url' target='_blank'&gt;",
            "&lt;a href='url' new&gt;",
            "&lt;a href='url' target='new'&gt;",
            "&lt;a href='url' target='new_tab'&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12: Which of these elements are all <table> elements?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;table&gt;, &lt;tr&gt;, &lt;tt&gt;",
            "&lt;thead&gt;, &lt;body&gt;, &lt;tr&gt;",
            "&lt;table&gt;, &lt;tr&gt;, &lt;td&gt;",
            "&lt;table&gt;, &lt;head&gt;, &lt;tfoot&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "13: Inline elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.",
        choices: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "14: How can you make an email link?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;mail href='mailto:example@example.com'&gt;",
            "&lt;a href='mailto:example@example.com'&gt;",
            "&lt;a href='email@example.com'&gt;",
            "&lt;mail&gt;example@example.com&lt;/mail&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "15: How do you insert a comment in HTML?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;!-- This is a comment --&gt;",
            "'This is a comment",
            "&lt;comment&gt;This is a comment&lt;/comment&gt;",
            "// This is a comment"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "16: Which HTML element is used to define the title of a document?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;meta&gt;",
            "&lt;title&gt;",
            "&lt;head&gt;",
            "&lt;header&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "17: Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
        choices: [
            "font",
            "class",
            "styles",
            "style"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "18: Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?",
        choices: [
            "title",
            "src",
            "alt",
            "longdesc"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "19: What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;video&gt;",
            "&lt;movie&gt;",
            "&lt;media&gt;",
            "&lt;play&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "20: What is the correct HTML for making a text area?",
        choices: [
            "&lt;textfield&gt;",
            "&lt;textarea&gt;",
            "&lt;input type='textarea'&gt;",
            "&lt;input type='textbox'&gt;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    }
];
